Inventory of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos Collection AD.RG.009.3-2-1
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos
Fall 2013 - Spring 2020
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
AD.RG.009.3-2-1
84.14 Gigabytes in 5,040 computer files
The NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos collection is a collection of digital images, as well as some music and video files, from a variety of student and campus events during Academic Years 2014 - 2020.
Biographical / Historical
Programs of NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life, part of the Division of Student Affairs (previously Campus Life), include a variety of events and activities organized to cultivate engagement and inclusivity across the NYUAD campus. The Manager of Campus Facilities is part of a team of staff that advises on and arranges space and services to ensure events are successful. This includes photography and audiovisual arrangements. Historically, the Campus Facilities Managers have retained audiovisual content from events, especially in the institution's first decade.
Content Description
The NYU Abu Dhabi Student Life Events: Photos, Music, and Videos collection is a collection of digital images, as well as some music and video files, from a variety of student and campus events during Academic Years 2014 - 2020. The collection was maintained, organized and transferred to the University Archives by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall. Dowdall also transferred files he inherited from his predecessor, Alex Heald.
Events that are documented range from student field trips, to campus festivals, to other campus events such as Autism Awareness Week, Latino Night, Marhaba, Staff Appreciation Day, and Defend the Nest, among others. Many of these events were, and some still are, understood as "campus traditions" during the institution's first decade.
A small file of administrative and program records labeled "Student Life Coordinator," were also transferred as part of this collection.
Arrangement
The collection has been minimally processed and its original arrangement by academic year has been retained.
Conditions Governing Access
This digital collection is accessible to members of the NYU Abu Dhabi community and the NYU Global Network.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual material is born-digital and available for viewing on a computer workstation in the Archives and Special Collections Reading Room, facilitated by ASC staff. View-only remote access may be available, contact nyuad-asc-group@nyu.edu to request access.
- Student Life Event Coordinator, Fall 2013 - Spring 2015; 34.7 Megabytes
  Scope and Contents
  Mixed program and administrative files.
  - Student Life Brochure, June 20, 2013; 1 Sheets; 34.7 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-001)
    A draft copy of the 2013 Student Life brochure, with markups by Josh Taylor.
  - Budget, January-March, 2014; 2 Sheets; 34 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-002)
  - FileRelease, circa 2013; 2.4 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-003)
  - Flavors of Abu Dhabi, January - April, 2014; 2 Sheets; .0021 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-004)
  - Forms, 2014; 1 Sheets; .0017 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-005)
  - Linajma, 2013-2014; 6.4 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-006)
  - Ma_a Salama, 2015; 1 Sheets; .0014 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-007)
  - Marhaba, 2013; 1 Sheets; .0013 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-008)
  - Marhaba, 2014; .0417 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-009)
  - Newsletter, Fall 2013, Fall 2014, Spring 2015; .0214 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-010)
  - NYUAD Brand Pack, 2010-2011; 19.6 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-011)
  - Saadiyat, 2013; .0487 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-012)
  - Student Info, NYU NY, Fall 2013; .0053 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-013)
    Appraisal
    This document contains student PII (netID), may need to be redacted before providing access.
- AY13-14 (Alex Heald), Fall 2013 - Spring 2014; 429.7 Megabytes
  Images and documents maintained by the Manager of Student Life Facilities, Alex Heald, from the period 2013-2014.
  - Ajman Kashtah, 136 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-014)
  - AustraliaNZ, 51.2 Megabytes (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-015)
  - Autism Event (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-016)
  - Breakthrough (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-017)
  - Class of 2014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-018)
  - Dubai Kashtah (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-019)
  - Fujairah Camping (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-020)
  - GIN [Global Issues Network] 2014 (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-021)
  - HULT (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-022)
  - Latino Night (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-023)
  - Linajma (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-024)
  - Mangroves (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-025)
  - National Day (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-026)
  - Old Photos (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-027)
  - Random (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-028)
  - Sama Cup Outreach (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-029)
  - Saudi VIP (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-030)
  - Taste From Home Malaysian (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-031)
  - USA Canada Night (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_RG_009_3_2_1-032)
- AY14-15 (Alex Heald), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 1.67 Gigabytes
  Includes images from a variety of events and field trips, maintained by Student Life Facilities Manager Alex Heald.
- AY14-15 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2014 - Spring 2015; 483.6 Megabytes
  Images and audio files from academic year 2014-2015, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
- AY15-16 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2015 - Spring 2016; 3.83 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2015-2016, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
- AY16-17 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2016 - Spring 2017; 14.85 Gigabytes
  Images from academic year 2016-2017, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
- AY17-18 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2017 - Spring 2018; 27.14 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2017-2018, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
- AY18-19 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2018 - Spring 2019; 7.2 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2018-2019, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.
- AY19-20 (Declan Dowdall), Fall 2019 - Spring 2020; 28.5 Gigabytes
  Images and some audiovisual files from academic year 2019-2020, maintained by Student Affairs Facilities Manager, Declan Dowdall.